

## MUHAMMAD RAMDHANI

🔇 082210403837 | M mramdhani2112@gmail.com | 🗘 | in | 💳 Portofolio

Jatiuwung, Kota Tangerang, Banten

I am a passionate data analyst who thrives on solving problems using insights drawn from data. I graduated from Mercu Buana University with a degree in Information Systems, and I specialize in analyzing data, automating processes in real-time, and creating clear data visualizations. Having worked for a year processing tracer study data, I have honed my skills in transforming data into practical outcomes.

### **Work Experience**

#### Mercu Buana University - Biro Karir, Hubungan dan Penelusuran Alumni

Apr 2022 - Present

West Jakarta, DKI Jakarta

Internship Data Analyst

- Developed a Tracer Study questionnaire for D3, S1, S2 and S3
- Processing more than 32.000 alumni Tracer Study data in five year and then visualizing it into diagrams and tables according to company needs.
- Successfully reported raw data from the results of the questionnaire in accordance with the website code tracerstudy.kemdikbud.go.id.
- Developed a Tracer Study questionnaire for D3, S1, S2 and S3

#### PT. Atlasfizl Meraki Inovasi - West Jakarta, DKI Jakarta

Feb 2022 - May 2022

UI/UX Intern

- · Analysis of the User Interface design of User Interface sertifikatku.id
- Re-design the User Interface design of the sertifikatku.id website using Figma.
- Create a User Experience prototype for the website.

#### **Education Level**

Mercu Buana University - West Jakarta, DKI Jakarta 📀

Sep 2019 - Aug 2023

Bachelor Degree in Information Systems, 3.72/4.00

- Chief Executive of the Ruang Karya 2022: UI/UX Workshop and Competition with the theme "Build Generational Skills Using O Digital Technology in The Era of Technological Development"
- Transcript Value ②

SMAN 11 Tangerang - Kota Tangerang, Banten

Sep 2016 - Aug 2019

High School Diploma in Social Science

# Organisational Experience

Student Executive Board of the Faculty of Computer Science, University of Mercu Buana 🔾

Oct 2021 - Jun 2022

West Jakarta, DKI Jakarta

Members of the Scientific Division

- Leading a team in planning, coordinating, and executing a UI/UX workshop and competition with the theme "Build Generational Skills Using Digital Technology in The Era of Technological Development."
- Selecting relevant and engaging topics for workshop sessions, and designing a well-structured program to encompass presentation sessions and competition segments.
- · Collaborating with partners, sponsors, and external speakers in event planning.
- Managing event promotion and marketing through social media, and other promotional materials to reach the appropriate target audience.
- Being responsible for presentation equipment, catering, and other technical requirements.

## Information Systems Student Association, Mercu Buana University 🔾

Oct 2020 - Jun 2021

West Jakarta, DKI Jakarta

Members of the Religious Division

- · Organized communication channels between teams, participants, and stakeholders for the "Bukber" Ramadan event.
- · Managed event details and information dissemination to ensure participants were well-informed.
- Coordinated technical support and documented event progress for future reference.

#### **Skills**

• Programming: PHP, Javascript, CSS, SQL, Code Igniter 3, • Tools: Visual Studio Code, Sublime Text 3, Jupyter Notebook Python Anaconda3

- Analysis, Tables & Visualization: Formula, SQL, Tables, Tools: Spreadsheet, Excels, SQL, High Charts Charts
- · Design & Visual
- Business Process Analyst : BPMN, Use Case, Activity, etc
- · Forms, Web Page Googe Script

- Tools: Figma, Canva & PowerPoint
- Tools: Bizagi Modeler, Visual Paradigm
- Tools: Google Forms, Google Apps Script, Forms.app

#### Sertificate

- Certified Secure Computer User (CSCU) v2 (2020): EC-Council
- Database Design (2021): Oracle Academy
- PL/SQL Database Programming (2021): Oracle Academy
- Primavera P6 Professional Project Management Fundamentals (2022): Oracle Academy
- BNSP Programmer and Software Development Certification : Junior Web Programmer (2023): LSP Telematika
- Intro to Front-end Development (2023): Digitalent Scholarship Fresh Graduate Academy & Progate
- PCAP: Programming Essentials in Python 📀 (2023): Cisco Networking Academy & OpenEDG Python Institute